https://lonang.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you contact us.
When contacting us, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also gather non-personally identifiable information when you visit our site, solely for the purpose of logging traffic, counting page views, and similar purposes.
None of this information can be traced back to you.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used to improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
Do we use cookies?
No.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.lonang.com/terms-use/
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on May 31, 2012.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Lonang Institute37637 5 Mile Rd. #397Livonia, Michigan 48154USAhttp://www.lonang.com/contact-us/
Copyright © 2014-2020 LONANG INSTITUTE.
All Rights Reserved.
About Us
Contact Us
0
